Guide to the Johan Kugelberg punk collection, circa 1974-1986.
Kugelberg, Johan punk collection
- Series I. Magazines and Fanzines
  - Happyland, 2001-2002; Issue #: 9-11 (Box 3, Folder 34)
    Notes: #9 resumes after a hiatus (1-8 published 1991-1993)
  - Hard Rock Comics, 1992-06; Issue #: 4 (Box 3, Folder 35)
    Publication location: San Diego, CA, United States
    Editors: Todd Loren
    Notes: Bio comic of Nirvana; written by Spike Steffenhagen; art by Scott Pentzer
  - Harsh Reality, 1980; Issue #: 10 (Box 3, Folder 36)
    Publication location: Ipswich, Suffolk, Great Britain
    Editors: Laurence
  - Heat, 1977-1978; Issue #: 4, 6-9 (Box 3, Folder 37)
    Publication location: Dublin, Northern Ireland, Great Britain
    Editors: Pete Price
  - High Times, February, 1977; Issue #: 18 (Box 8, Folder 27)
    Editors: Pamela Lloyd Shakespear
  - High Times, February, 1977; Issue #: 18 (Box 24, Folder 33)
  - High Times, 1978; Issue #: 33-34 (Box 3, Folder 38)
    Editors: Shelley Levitt
    Notes: "Punk Magazine no. 0" insert
  - High Times, 1983-09; Issue #: 97 (Box 3, Folder 38)
    Editors: Larry Sloman
  - Hoe, 1994-1995; Issue #: 1-3 (Box 3, Folder 39)
    Publication location: State College, PA, United States
    Editors: Allan Horrocks
  - Holmstrom, John [miscellaneous comics], Issue #: 19702 (Box 25, Folder 27)
  - Hoopla, 1977; Issue #: 1-5 (Box 3, Folder 40)
    Publication location: Peoria, IL, United States
    Editors: Jon Ginoli
  - Horses, 1977; Issue #: 2 (Box 3, Folder 41)
    Publication location: Middlesex, Great Britain
    Editors: Nick Palamino
  - Horseshit: The Offensive Review, 1965; Issue #: 1 (Box 3, Folder 42)
    Publication location: Hermosa Beach, CA, United States
    Editors: Robert M. Dunker, Thomas W. Dunker
  - Hot Cha, 1970?; Issue #: 49 (Box 3, Folder 43)
    Publication location: Zurich, Switzerland
    Editors: Urban G.
  - Hot On the Visuals (HOTV), 1980; Issue #: 3 (Box 3, Folder 44)
    Editors: Seg Gorham, Chris Burkham, Mick Garth
  - Humanbeing Lawnmower, 2007, 2009; Issue #: 1 (Box 3, Folder 45)
    Publication location: Astoria, NY, United States
    Editors: Avi Spivak
  - i-D, December, 2007; Issue #: 283 (Box 3, Folder 46)
    Notes: Pages 135-144 only, comprising an article on Linder Sterling.
  - Idle Thoughts, 1984; Issue #: 8 (Box 3, Folder 47)
    Publication location: Delta, BC, Canada
    Editors: Len Morgan
  - If and Only If, 1971; Issue #: [1] (Box 3, Folder 48)
    Publication location: Dunkirk, NY, United States
    Editors: Tom Bingham
  - If In Doubt Consult Dealer, April, 1970; Volume #: 1, Issue #: 1 (Box 3, Folder 49)
    Publication location: Saugus, CA, United States
    Editors: John Ingham
  - Illustrated Ape, 2003; Issue #: 15 (Box 24, Folder 19)
    Editors: Christian Pattison, Michael Sims
  - In The City, 1978, 1980; Issue #: 6, 11, 15 (Box 3, Folder 50)
    Editors: Francis Drake, Peter Gilbert
  - In The Ditch, 198- (Box 3, Folder 51)
    Editors: Don Howe, Stella Marlowe
  - Infiltrator, 1978?; Issue #: 6 (Box 3, Folder 52)
    Publication location: Washington, DC, United States
    Editors: Marie Provost
  - Inside Out, 1978?; Issue #: 1 (Box 3, Folder 53)
    Editors: Derek Herdman
  - Intensive Care, 1980; Issue #: 1-2 (Box 3, Folder 54)
  - Into the Void, 1979; Issue #: 1 (Box 3, Folder 55)
    Publication location: Ely, Cambridgeshire, Great Britain
    Editors: Nigel Random
  - It's Only Rock n' Roll, 1977 (Box 3, Folder 56)
    Publication location: Vancouver, WA, United States
    Editors: Fred Seegmuller
  - Jah Ugliman, 1978, 1980, 198-; Issue #: 1-3 (Box 3, Folder 57)
    Publication location: Kingston, Jamaica
    Editors: Carl Gayle
  - Jamming, 1978; Issue #: 4-6 (Box 3, Folder 58)
    Editors: Anthony Fletcher
  - Jamming, 1979-1980; Issue #: 9-12 (Box 3, Folder 58)
  - Jazz & Pop, July, 1970; Volume #: 9, Issue #: 7 (Box 4, Folder 1)
    Editors: Patricia Kennely
  - Jewish Beatle, The, 1996; Issue #: 1 (Box 4, Folder 2)
    Publication location: Christchurch, New Zealand
    Editors: Duane Zarakov, Brother Evol
  - Judgement Times, 1981-Fall; Issue #: 1 (Box 4, Folder 3)
    Publication location: [Boston], United States
    Editors: Jah Twister, Tim Barry
  - Jungleland, November, 1977; Issue #: 6 (Box 4, Folder 4)
    Editors: Michael Scott
  - Kids Stuff, 1977-1978; Issue #: 1+, 2, 6, 8 (Box 4, Folder 5)
    Publication location: Chessington, Surrey, Great Britain
    Notes: "Special edited version"
  - Kill Your Pet Puppy, 1980; Issue #: 2-3 (Box 4, Folder 6)
    Editors: Street Joey Wise, Basil HawHaw, Benny Makhno, Anna Mal
  - Killin' Time, 1980; Issue #: 5 (Box 4, Folder 7)
    Publication location: Margate, Great Britain
    Editors: Paul Wright, Jonathan Todd
  - Kind Girls, 1981; Issue #: 2 (Box 4, Folder 8)
    Publication location: Cumbria, Great Britain
    Editors: Ali Tui, Tricia
  - King Harvest Review, 1971; Volume #: 2, Issue #: 3, 5 (Box 4, Folder 9)
    Publication location: Lawrence, KS, United States
    Editors: Robert C. Wilson
  - Kooks, January, 1989-November, 1911; Issue #: 2-8 (Box 4, Folder 10)
    Publication location: Allston, MA, United States
    Editors: Donna Kossy
  - LA Beat, 1978; Issue #: 1 (Box 4, Folder 11)
    Publication location: Long Beach, CA, United States
    Editors: Stephen Zepeda
    Notes: Missing p.13-16
  - LA Vision, May, 1982; Issue #: [1?] (Box 4, Folder 12)
    Publication location: Granada, Spain
  - Larm, March, July 1978; Issue #: 7 (Box 4, Folder 13)
    Editors: Lennart Persson
  - Larm, 1983; Issue #: 16 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Let it Rock, 1972-February, 1973; Issue #: 3-5 (Box 4, Folder 14)
    Editors: Dave Laing
  - Let it Rock, April-May, 1973; Issue #: 7-8 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Let it Rock, June-November, 1973; Issue #: 9-14 (Box 4, Folder 15)
    Editors: Dave Laing, John Pidgeon
  - Let it Rock, January, June, December, 1974; Issue #: 16, 21, 24 (Box 4, Folder 16)
    Editors: John Pidgeon
  - Let it Rock, July, 1974; Issue #: 22 (Box 8, Folder 28)
    Publication location: Great Britain
  - Let it Rock, January-July, 1975; Issue #: 25-31 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Let it Rock, October, 1975; Issue #: 34 (Box 8, Folder 28)
  - Let's Be Adult About This, 1979; Issue #: 1 (Box 4, Folder 18)
    Editors: Vicki Bonnet, Jimmi Thirlwell
  - Life in a Void, 1981?; Issue #: 5b (Box 4, Folder 19)
    Publication location: Kent, Great Britain
  - Life Sucks Die, 2000; Issue #: 6 (Box 4, Folder 20)
    Editors: Khaki Bikini, Alvin Karpis, Pete Vuckovich, Hector Cerveza Fria
  - Liquorice, 1975-1976; Issue #: 2, 4-5 (Box 4, Folder 21)
    Publication location: Nottingham, Great Britain
  - Live Wire, 1977; Issue #: 1-2, 11 (Box 4, Folder 22)
    Editors: Alan Thunder/Anger
  - Living Color, The, March, 1982 (Box 4, Folder 23)
    Editors: Jack Stevenson
  - Lobotomy, March-June, 1978; Volume #: 1, Issue #: 4-7 (Box 4, Folder 24)
    Publication location: Los Angeles, CA, United States
    Editors: Pleasant, Randy Detroit
  - Lobotomy, April, August, 1979; Volume #: 2, Issue #: 3-4 (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - London's Burning, December, 1976; Issue #: 1a (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - London's Outrage, 1976, 1978; Issue #: 1-2 (Box 4, Folder 26)
    Editors: John Savage
  - Lowdown, The, June 1955; Volume #: 1, Issue #: no. 3 (Box 4, Folder 27)
    Publication location: Canton, OH, United States
    Editors: Joel Raleigh
  - Ludd's Mill, 1971-1973; Issue #: 3-4, 6-8 (Box 4, Folder 28)
    Publication location: Huddersfield, Yorkshire, Great Britain
  - Ludd's Mill, 1976, 1978; Issue #: 14, 15, 18 (Box 4, Folder 28)
    Publication location: Ossett, West Yorkshire, Great Britain
  - Ludd's Mill, 1978?; Issue #: 16/17 (Box 8, Folder 29)
    Editors: Andrew Darlington
  - Mad, June, 1978; Issue #: 199 (Box 4, Folder 29)
  - Magazine X, 1977; Issue #: [1?] (Box 4, Folder 30)
    Publication location: Portland, OR, United States
    Editors: M King
    Notes: Sex Pistols USA tour review
  - Marble Index, the, 1971 (Box 4, Folder 31)
    Publication location: Arlington, VA, United States
    Editors: "Space Comandos"
  - Maximumrocknroll, July, 1984; Issue #: 15 (Box 4, Folder 32)
    Notes: Cover story on collecting punk
  - Mellow, November, 1977; Issue #: Suppl. (Box 4, Folder 33)
    Publication location: Lakewood, OH, United States
    Editors: Jack Springer
    Notes: With manuscript note to Greg Shaw
  - Mental Children, 1980; Issue #: 1 (Box 4, Folder 34)
  - Mental Mapping, 1981? (Box 24, Folder 20)
  - Metanoia, 1970-1072; Issue #: 3, 8,10-11 (Box 4, Folder 35)
    Publication location: Fairfax, CA, United States
    Notes: Alt. title: Karnis Bottle's Metanoia
  - Midnight Man: The Davey Graham Fanzine, 1999-2001; Issue #: 1-3 (Box 4, Folder 36)
    Publication location: York, Great Britain
    Editors: Kay Thomson
  - Misfits, 1982-83? (Box 4, Folder 37)
    Publication location: [Great Britain?]
  - Modern World, 1977; Issue #: 1 (Box 4, Folder 38)
    Publication location: Raleigh, NC, United States
    Editors: Butch Wax
  - More-On-Four, 1977 (Box 24, Folder 20)
    Publication location: [London], Great Britain
    Notes: Corner safety-pinned
  - Muckraker, 1996-2000; Issue #: 6-9 (Box 4, Folder 39)
    Editors: Patrick Marley
    Notes: Includes a 7" record
  - Musician, Issue #: 24 (Box 4, Folder 40)
    Publication location: Gloucester, MA, United States
    Editors: Sam Holdsworth
    Notes: Cover detached
  - Musikens Makt, 1974; Issue #: 5 (Box 24, Folder 20)
    Publication location: Göteborg, Sweden
    Editors: Figge Lorentzen
  - National Screw, November, 1976; Volume #: 1, Issue #: 1 (Box 4, Folder 41)
    Publication location: Secaucus, NJ, United States
    Editors: Al Goldstein
  - Negative Reaction, February-October, 1978; Issue #: 5, 7 (Box 4, Folder 42)
    Publication location: Cambridge, Great Britain
    Editors: Jon Romney
  - Never Trust a Hippie, 1993; Issue #: 1-3 (Box 4, Folder 43)
    Publication location: Alcester, Warwickshire, Great Britain
    Editors: Jim Henderson, Neil McLean
  - Never Trust a Hippie, 1993-1994; Issue #: 5, 7-8 (Box 4, Folder 43)
    Editors: Jim Henderson
  - Never Trust a Hippie, 1995-1996; Issue #: 10, 12-13 (Box 4, Folder 43)
  - New Age, January, 1978 (Box 4, Folder 44)
    Publication location: Greensboro, NC, United States
    Editors: Nancy New Age
  - New Diseases (See note re:title), 1977?; [1?] (Box 4, Folder 45)
    Publication location: [San Francisco], United States
    Editors: Jean Caffeine
    Notes: Title spelling varies from issue to issue. This issue is "New Dezezes."
  - New Magazine, A, 1979; Issue #: 1 (Box 4, Folder 46)
    Publication location: Pittsburgh, PA, United States
    Editors: Bill Bored, Ernie Hitler
    Notes: Includes typescript letter from editor to Greg Shaw.
  - New Order, 1977; Issue #: 1-2 (Box 4, Folder 47)
    Publication location: Dania, FL, United States
    Editors: R. Mascaro, James Marshall
  - New Times, May, 1970; Volume #: 1, Issue #: 2 (Box 26, Folder 3)
    Editors: Jonathan Kundra
  - New Wave Magazine, The, 1977; Issue #: 2-3 (Box 4, Folder 48)
    Publication location: New Barnet, Hertsfordshire, Great Britain
    Editors: 1st Ade
  - New Wave Magazine, The, May, 1977; Issue #: 5 (Box 8, Folder 30)
    Editors: Sex-Ade
  - New Wave News, 1977; Issue #: 1-3 (Box 4, Folder 49)
    Editors: Vic Lime
    Notes: Folds out into poster
  - New Wave Rock, September, November 1978; Volume #: 1, Issue #: 1-2 (Box 4, Folder 50)
    Editors: Diana Clapton
  - Next Big Thing, The, 1977-1978; Issue #: 1, 4-5, 8 (Box 4, Folder 51)
    Publication location: Stirlingshire, Scotland, Great Britain
    Editors: Lindsay Hutton
  - Next Big Thing, The, 1979-1981; Issue #: 9-12 (Box 4, Folder 51)
    Notes: Also numbered vol. 2 no. 1
  - Next Big Thing, The, 1981-1982; Issue #: 13-15 (Box 4, Folder 52)
    Notes: Includes manuscript letter to Greg Shaw.
  - Next Big Thing, The, 1986-1987; Issue #: 21, 23 (Box 4, Folder 52)
    Notes: With two mini-zines (issued with this number): Watch This #4 and This Stuff'll Kill Ya! #1.
  - Next Big Thing, The/Rockin' Bones, 1985; Issue #: 20/10 (Box 4, Folder 52)
    Notes: Split issue, tete-beche: Next Big Thing #20 and Rockin' Bones #10. Includes manuscript letter to Greg Shaw.
  - NMX (New Musickal Excess), 1979-1980; Issue #: 6, 14, 17 (Box 4, Folder 53)
    Editors: Martin Russian
  - No, 1978-1979; Volume #: 1, Issue #: 1 (Box 4, Folder 54)
    Publication location: [New York?], United States
    Editors: Joseph Brainiac
  - No Exit, 1977; Issue #: 1?, 2 (Box 4, Folder 55)
    Publication location: San Francisco, CA, United States
    Editors: Tony Steel
  - No Fun, December, 1977-November, 1978; Issue #: 2-12 (Box 5, Folder 1)
    Editors: Peter Preissle, Urs Steiger
  - No Fun, December, 1978-1979; Issue #: 13-16 (Box 5, Folder 2)
    Notes: Flier laid in
  - No Future (France), 1977-1979? (Box 5, Folder 3)
    Publication location: France
    Notes: French translations of Sex Pistols, Clash lyrics
  - Noise, April, 1981; Issue #: 2 (Box 5, Folder 4)
    Publication location: Venia, OH, United States
    Editors: Bob Moore
  - Noize, 1977-1978; Volume #: 1, Issue #: 2, 8 (Box 5, Folder 5)
    Publication location: Portland, OR,
    Editors: Fred Seegmuller, Rozz Rezabek
  - Nomag, 1982-1983; . 1-3 (Box 26, Folder 3)
    Editors: Bruce Kalberg
  - Not New Wave News, April, 1979; Issue #: 1 (Box 8, Folder 31)
    Editors: CR Cramp, Rumor
  - Now/Then, 197-; Issue #: 3/1 (Box 5, Folder 6)
    Editors: Chris
    Notes: Split publication (by same editor): "Now" #3 (mainly punk); last few pages are "Then" #1 (mainly reggae)
  - Nu Yu, 1997-Summer; Issue #: 1 (Box 5, Folder 7)
    Publication location: Philadelphia, PA, United States
    Editors: Daniel Silk, Julian Kernes, Mark Kernes
  - Number Two, 1998?; Issue #: 10 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Nyp, December, 1977; Issue #: 13 (Box 5, Folder 9)
    Editors: Solomon Spector
    Notes: Continued from O. Rexstasy, returns to that title after this issue.
  - O. Rextasy, July, 1974; Issue #: 3 (Box 5, Folder 10)
    Editors: Solomon & Jay Gruberger
  - Offense, The, 1981; Issue #: 7 (Box 5, Folder 11)
    Publication location: Columbus, OH, United States
    Editors: TKA
  - Okej, 1982; Issue #: 8 (Box 5, Folder 12)
    Publication location: Stockholm, Sweden
  - OP, January-September, 1983; 1984; Issue #: Q-S, X (Box 5, Folder 13)
    Publication location: Olympia, WA, United States
    Editors: John Foster
    Notes: Issues are lettered rather than numbered; each issue covers bands beginning with the theme letter.
  - Opprobrium, July, 1998; Issue #: 4 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Option: Music Alternatives, October, 1987; Issue #: P2 (Box 5, Folder 15)
    Editors: Scott Becker
    Notes: Continued from OP.
  - Out Crowd, 1975; Issue #: 1 (Box 5, Folder 16)
    Editors: Karen Dyson
    Notes: Includes letter to Greg Shaw
  - Outasite, after 1978; Issue #: 2 (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Outlet, 1979-March, 1981; Issue #: 9, 14, 17, 22 (Box 5, Folder 18)
    Publication location: Ilford, Essex, Great Britain
    Editors: Trev Faull
  - Outlet, April 1982-1984?; Issue #: 25, 27-29 (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Oz, May, 1970; Issue #: 28 (Box 8, Folder 32)
    Publication location: UK
    Editors: Richard Neville, Felix Dennis, Jim Anderson
  - Panache, 1977; [1?] (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Panache, 1977, 1980; Issue #: 4, 13 (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Panic in LA, 1980; Issue #: 2 (Box 5, Folder 20)
    Editors: Dinky Grant, Michelle Baer
  - Passion Fruit Prison, 1996?; Issue #: 1 (Box 5, Folder 21)
    Publication location: Toronto, Ontario, Canada
    Notes: Includes 7" record
  - Patio X Table, 1983; Issue #: 2 (Box 24, Folder 21)
    Publication location: Seattle, WA,
    Editors: Sue Ann Harkey
    Notes: Top/side stapled
  - Penetration, 1975, 1977; Issue #: 7, 10-12 (Box 5, Folder 22)
    Publication location: Stockport, Great Britain
    Editors: Paul Welsh
  - Penthouse, December, 1972; Volume #: 4, Issue #: 4 (Box 5, Folder 23)
    Editors: Bob Guccione
  - Penthouse, February, 1975; Volume #: 6, Issue #: 6 (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - Penthouse, 1975, 1976; Volume #: 7, Issue #: 2,7 (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - Penthouse, October, 1976; Volume #: 8, Issue #: 2 (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - Phfudd!, 1987, 1978; Issue #: 9, 12 (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - Pig Paper, 1977-1978; Issue #: 3, 5-6, 8, 10 (Box 5, Folder 26)
    Publication location: Missauga, Ontario, Canada
  - Pig Paper, 1980, 1982; Issue #: 11-14 (Box 5, Folder 26)
    Editors: Gary Pig Gold
  - Pig Paper, 1985; Issue #: 16-17 (Box 5, Folder 26)
  - Pink Flag, 1981; Issue #: 7-8 (Box 5, Folder 27)
    Editors: Pat Mackle
    Notes: Includes flier for the fanzine Cabaret
  - Popen I Dag, 1975/1976; Issue #: 1975-1978 (Box 5, Folder 28)
    Publication location: Sweden
    Editors: Stig Norglund
  - Popwatch, 1998; Issue #: 9 (Box 5, Folder 29)
    Publication location: Somerville, MA, United States
    Editors: Leslie Gaffney
  - Poser, 1977-1978; Issue #: 1-2 (Box 24, Folder 21)
    Editors: Danny Destroy
  - Praxis, 1980; Issue #: 6 (Box 5, Folder 30)
    Publication location: Chicago, IL and New York, United States
    Notes: Includes flexidisc
  - Prehistoric Sounds, 1994-1996; Volume #: 1, Issue #: 1-4 (Box 5, Folder 31)
    Editors: Ian McFarlane
  - Pressure Drop, 1972-73?; Issue #: 2 (Box 5, Folder 32)
    Editors: Nick Kimberley, Chris Lane, Peter Simons
  - Pretentious Fanzine, 1980; Issue #: 1 (Box 5, Folder 33)
    Publication location: Surrey, Great Britain
    Editors: Martin Brown
  - Propaganda, 1984-1988; Issue #: 3,4,6-10 (Box 5, Folder 34)
    Publication location: New Hyde Park, NY, United States
    Editors: Fred H. Berger
  - Prurient Interest, 1983?; Volume #: 1, Issue #: 1 (Box 5, Folder 35)
    Publication location: Cambridge, MA, United States
    Editors: John Stevenson
  - Psychotronic Video, 1989-Spring; Issue #: 2 (Box 5, Folder 36)
    Editors: Michael J. Weldon
  - Ptolemaic Terrascope, April, 1992; Volume #: 3, Issue #: 2 (whole no. 10) (Box 5, Folder 37)
    Editors: Phil McMullen
  - Ptolemaic Terrascope, February, 1995; Issue #: 18 (Box 5, Folder 37)
  - Punk, 2007-Fall; Issue #: 21 (Box 5, Folder 38)
    Editors: John Holmstrom
    Notes: Signed on cover by Roberta Bayley. Special "tribute to CBGB" issue.
  - Punk, January 1975 - June 1979; Issue #: 1 (2 copies), 2-3, 5-8, 10-12, 14-17 (Box 33)
    Publication location:New York, NY, United States
  - Punk: Special Magazine [D.O.A. the Official Filmbook], April 1981; Issue #: 1 (Box 33)
  - Punk Globe, November, 1979 (Box 5, Folder 39)
    Editors: Ginger Coyote
  - Punk Lust, 1981?; Issue #: 5 (Box 5, Folder 40)
    Editors: Wilum Pugmyr
  - Punk Magazine, 1976-1977 (Box 25, Folder 28)
  - Punk Magazine, 1977-1978 (Box 25, Folder 29)
  - Punk Magazine, 1978-1979 (Box 25, Folder 30)
  - Punk Magazine, 2001, 2007 (Box 25, Folder 31)
  - Punk Magazine [related ephemera], 1976 (Box 8, Folder 33)
    Notes: Pamphlet soliciting advertisers for Punk Magazine
  - Punk Magazine [related ephemera], ca. 1976 (Box 8, Folder 33)
    Notes: Bumper sticker reading "Watch Out! Punk is Here!"
  - Punk Magazine [related ephemera], ca. 1977 (Box 8, Folder 33)
    Notes: Business Card for Roberta Bayley, "Ace Photog"
  - Punk Magazine [related ephemera], ca. 1978 (Box 8, Folder 33)
    Notes: Business Card for Legs McNeil, "Resident Punk"
  - Punk Magazine [related ephemera] (Box 25, Folder 32)
  - Punk Magazine Awards Ceremony material (Box 29, Folder 5)
  - Punk Magazine calendar, 1979 (Box 24, Folder 10)
  - Punk Rock, February, April 1978; Volume #: 2, Issue #: 1, 2 (Box 5, Folder 41)
    Editors: Jeff Goodman
  - Punk Rock Special: Sex Pistols, 1978-Spring; Volume #: 1, Issue #: 1 (Box 5, Folder 42)
    Notes: Covers detached
  - Punk Rock Stars, July, 1978; Issue #: 8 (Box 5, Folder 43)
    Editors: Pat Farewell
  - Punk Scene, The, 1977 (Box 5, Folder 44)
    Editors: Pat Johnstone, John Barraclough
    Notes: Folds out into poster. "Chart Toppers Magazine Special 3."
  - Puritan, 1977; Volume #: 1, Issue #: 1 (Box 5, Folder 45)
    Publication location: Northampton, PA, United States
    Editors: Jeffrey Price Michelson
  - Ramones Unofficial Fan Club, 1977; Issue #: 6 (Box 5, Folder 46)
    Notes: With manuscript corrections to text
  - Rapid Eye Movement, 1979-Winter; Issue #: 1 (Box 5, Folder 47)
    Editors: Simon D.
  - Raunch and Roll, October, 1975; Issue #: 4 (Box 5, Folder 48)
    Editors: Jay Gruberger
  - Reason, 1997; Volume #: 29, Issue #: 4 (Box 8, Folder 34)
    Editors: Virginia I. Postrel
  - Record Collector, January, 2003; Issue #: 281 (Box 5, Folder 49)
    Editors: Andy Davis
    Notes: "Punk special."
  - Record Raves, May, 1977; Volume #: 1, Issue #: 1 (Box 5, Folder 50)
    Publication location: Stone Harbor, NJ, United States
    Editors: Charles P. Lamey
  - Reggae Connection, The, August, 1981; Volume #: 1, Issue #: 1 (Box 5, Folder 51)
    Editors: Sista Jah
  - Return to Whatever, 1977?; Issue #: 1 (Box 5, Folder 52)
    Publication location: [Washington, D.C.?], United States
    Editors: Mike Livewire
  - Revenge, August, 1977; Issue #: 3 (Box 5, Folder 53)
  - Ripped & Torn, November, 1976-April, 1977; Issue #: 1-4 (Box 6, Folder 1)
    Editors: Tony D.
  - Ripped & Torn, 1977; Issue #: 5, 6, 9 (Box 6, Folder 1)
    Editors: Sandy Robertson
  - Ripped & Torn, 1978-1979; Issue #: 10-11, 14-16, 18 (Box 6, Folder 2)
    Notes: Includes manuscript letter from editor to Greg Shaw.
  - Ripper, 1981?; Issue #: 5 (Box 6, Folder 3)
    Publication location: San Jose, CA, United States
    Editors: Tim Tonooka
  - Rock & Folk, March, 1978; Issue #: 134 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Rock Marketplace, 1973; Volume #: 1, Issue #: 1-2 (Box 6, Folder 5)
    Publication location: Elmhurst, NY, United States
    Editors: Alan Betrock
  - Rock Marketplace, 1973-1975; Volume #:, Issue #: 3, 5-6, 8-9 (Box 6, Folder 5)
    Notes: With a laid-in update sheet.
  - Rock News, 1975-September, 1976; Issue #: 1-3, 6-7 (Box 6, Folder 6)
    Editors: Michel Esteban
  - Rock News, 1976; Issue #: Hors Serie (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Rockerilla, February, 1982-January, 1983; Issue #: 21, 28, 30 (Box 6, Folder 7)
    Publication location: Cairo Montenotte, Italy
    Editors: Gianpaolo Carlini
  - Rocket From the Tombs Mutual Admiration Society Newsletter & Guide, ca. 1974?; Volume #: 1, Issue #: 2 (Box 6, Folder 8)
    Editors: Stella Rayon
    Notes: Photocopied facsimile
  - Rockin' Bones, 1986?; Issue #: 11 (Box 6, Folder 9)
    Notes: See also "Next Big Thing."
  - Roctober, 2002; Issue #: 33-34 (Box 6, Folder 10)
    Publication location: Chicago, IL, United States
    Editors: Jake Austen
    Notes: Includes CD
  - Rollerderby, 1991-1993; Issue #: 2/3, 3-11 (Box 6, Folder 11)
    Publication location: Dover, NH, United States
    Editors: Lisa Suckdog (Lisa Crystal Carver)
    Notes: 1993 reprint of issues 2 and 3.
  - Rollerderby, 1993-1995; Issue #: 12-15, 17-18 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Rollerderby, 1997-1999; Issue #: 20-25 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Rollin' Rock, 1972; Issue #: 8, 11 (Box 6, Folder 14)
    Editors: Ron Weiser
  - Rollin' Rock, 1977; Issue #: 15 (Box 6, Folder 14)
    Publication location: Van Nuys, CA, United States
  - Rough Trade, August, 1982; Issue #: 11 (Box 26, Folder 4)
    Publication location: Tokyo, Japan
    Editors: Noe Serizawa
    Notes: Unbound
  - San Jose Skate Ripper Magazine, 1981-82?; Issue #: 1 (Box 6, Folder 15)
    Editors: Craig S. Ramsay
  - Septic Ears, 1977; Issue #: [1] (Box 26, Folder 4)
    Editors: Ivan Ardon
  - Sex, 2002-2003; Issue #: 2-3 (Box 6, Folder 16)
    Editors: Ika Johannesson
  - Shake It, 1977?; Issue #: 1 (Box 6, Folder 17)
    Publication location: Delaware, OH, United States
    Editors: D. Howland
  - Shakin' Street Gazette, October, 1974; Issue #: 14 (Box 6, Folder 18)
    Editors: Gary Sperrazza
  - Shews, 1977; Issue #: 2-3 (Box 6, Folder 19)